https://jacobsladderexercise.com/privacy-policy/

Checkout
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. Users have the option to create a username and password so that they may login and access information regarding their order or address later, but users may also make purchases as a guest.
For payment, data related to the order such as billing address, email, and order information is sent to PayPal for processing. Information is encrypted both on this website and PayPal. For more information on Privacy and PayPal visit https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full
Contact forms
When a user fills out and completes a form on this site, the entry is stored in the site database. Additionally, this information is sent to an authorized website administrator via email to notify them of the entry so they may follow up if needed. Users have the option to opt into receiving news, promotions, and other marketing material. If a user opts in, their email and name may be added to an email marketing list to receive future contact.
Cookies
If you have a representative account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
In addition, Google Analytics uses the following 3 cookies:
_ga     2 years       Used to distinguish users.
_gid   24 hours    Used to distinguish users.
_gat   1 minute    Used to throttle request rate.
For more information visit
https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage
To keep track of cart data, WooCommerce may make use of 3 cookies:
woocommerce_cart_hash
woocommerce_items_in_cart
wp_woocommerce_session_
The first two cookies contain information about the cart as a whole and helps WooCommerce know when the cart data changes. The final cookie (wp_woocommerce_session_) contains a unique code for each customer so that it knows where to find the cart data in the database for each customer. No personal information is stored within these cookies.
Additionally, this site uses Jetpack to speed up image processing and to automatically calculate tax rates. Jetpack uses several cookies:
tk_*r       Referral cookies used to analyse referrer behavior for Jetpack connected sites using WooCommerce.
tk_r3d     Security related
Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:
https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en
https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences
https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/
https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies
https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411
https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
This site uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic date to Google servers and helps us to understand how our site is used. Google Analytics does not collect personal data for individual users or associate your IP with any data it collects.
How long we retain your data
For registered partners on our website, we store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
Entries submitted through the contact form for Contact Requests or Quote applications are stored so that we can follow up, keep a record of consent (if any), and have a historical record of requests to the site. This information is stored indefinitely but can be deleted at any time if a user requests.
Our website is hosted by Flywheel, who may retain backups of the site and database for up to 30 day, after which they are deleted permanently. For more information about Flywheel and privacy visit https://getflywheel.com/legal/
Data is retained for orders and accounts in the following manner:
RETAIN INACTIVE ACCOUNTS:         2 years
RETAIN PENDING ORDERS:               2 weeks
RETAIN FAILED ORDERS:                   2 weeks
RETAIN CANCELLED ORDERS:         7 days
RETAIN COMPLETED ORDERS:        3 years
What rights you have over your data
You can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you including entries through forms or user accounts. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
To make a removal request, please contact info@jacobsladderexercise.com
Learn more about the cardio machines
you’ll love to hate.
Products
Contact
© Copyright 2018 Jacobs Ladder, LLC. All rights reserved.
6292 Walmore Rd., Niagara Falls, NY, 14304
Workouts
What People Say
Latest News
Parts
Equipment
Apparel
My account
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Store Locator
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
